

## **NGUYEN VAN A**

## **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and s nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit i of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum. 5 PARAGRAPHS COPY DISCOVER MO administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

## **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

## **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

## **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult bcaecati cupiditate non provident, similique sunt in culpa, qui officia deserunt mollitia animi and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

## **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to an occasional 'ing' or 'y' thrown in. It's ironic that when goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

**Recognition and Gains:** 

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

## **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

## CVPRO JSC

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer inc' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US at translating the almost-no

## **REFERENCES**



## **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

## **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt you how all this mistaken idea of denouncing pleasure and praising pain was b and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities